10秒の猶予をやる
I'll give you a count to ten.
Ten!
Nine!
Eight!
Seven!
Six!
Five!
出ていくしか…
I'll just have to go out!
Four!
いや
Actually,
気が変わった
I changed my mind.
One-Man Force
Episode 8
ナミ
Nami!
感じるぞ　貴様の怒りを
I can feel it!
The anger festering inside you!
俺への殺意が密林の隅々まで満ちている
Your urge to kill me...
I can feel it spreading to
every corner of the jungle!
まるで大気が震えているようだぞ　相良宗介
It's like the air itself is trembling,
Sagara Sousuke!
クラマ
Kurama!
出てこないのならそれでいい
If you don't want to come out,
that's fine too.
そのままこのくそ田舎にでも隠れてろ
You can keep hiding in this backwoods shithole.
ただ　これだけは言っておいてやる
Keep this in mind, however.
俺は貴様の大切なあの女も同じように扱ってやるぞ
I'm gonna make sure that precious girl
of yours meets the same fate!
Chidori!?
千鳥を
そうだ　俺は居場所を知っている
That's right!
I know where she is!
これからそこに帰って　この貧乏ったらしい娘にやったように
After I'm done here, I'll be heading that way to drill your woman full of holes,
お前の女もかましてやるぞ
the same way I did to this pitiful girl!
How dare you!
よくも
き…来ませんな
H-He's not coming out.
Yeah. Let's go.
行くぞ
伏せろ
Get down!
Enemy attack!
敵襲だ
7人　8人以上
Seven... Eight of them or more!
本字幕由诸神字幕组出品  仅供学习交流  禁止用于商业用途
何者だ
Who are they?
いやそれより
No, more importantly!
更多中日双语字幕  尽在 www.kamigami.org 和微博 @诸神字幕组
クラマ
Kurama!
日听&日校：小伍 gen   翻译&校对：mam 小江   时间轴：Foyzi   压制：結城結衣
なっ　貴様
Son of a—
Damn it!
くそ
撃つな　宗介
Don't shoot, Sousuke.
レモン
Lemon!
どういうことだ
What's going on here?
それは後だろ
That can wait.
間に合わなかった
We were too late.
なんてことだ
Oh, God...
Oh, God!
M-My force was completely wiped out!
わ…私の兵隊が殲滅されてしまった
どういうことだ　あの相良に仲間がいたのかね
How is this possible?
Did that Sagara guy have backup?
どうかな　連携が取れているようには見えなかった
Can't say for sure.
They didn't look like they were cooperating.
別の勢力だろ
It's probably a separate force.
で…では　何者が…
Th-Th-Then who could it be!?
知るか
How should I know?
Could it have been a trap from the start!?
まさか　最初から罠だったのでは
そ…そうだ　罠に違いない
Y-Yes! It couldn't have been anything else!
あなた方の間違った情報に踊らされて　私の兵隊たちはむざむざと
Thanks to faulty information on your end,
my troops got slaughtered!
うるさいぞ
Shut up.
C-Can't breathe...
…苦しい
よく聞け　俺は頭にきてる
Listen closely.
I am beyond pissed off.
お前の番犬どもは役立たずだし　あの小僧はまだ生きている
Your watchdogs have proven themselves useless,
and that brat is still alive because of it.
女を撃ったことも最悪だ
Shooting that girl was regrettable, too.
お前のような変態野郎なら　息子をおったてるところなんだろうが
Maybe perverts like you get off on killing kids,
俺は違う
but that's not who I am.
最低の気分だよ
I feel awful about it, you know?
そ…それです
A-About that...
なぜあの娘をあんなもったいないやり方で…
Why kill her?
And, in such a... wasteful manner...
あれで充分だ
Because it was enough.
ああすれば奴は必ず追ってくる
If I did that, he was sure to come after me.
俺を締め上げて殺さずにはいられんだろうさ
I doubt he'll be able to overcome his need to strangle me to death.
街で奴を迎え撃つぞ
I'm going to ambush him in the city.
あんたにも協力してもらう　わかったな
And you're going to help me.
Understand?
ミスタ・クラマ　この扱いは度が過ぎますぞ
Mr. Kurama!
This treatment is past your boundaries.
I do my part for the organization, and I oversee Namsac!
私とて組織に貢献し　ナムサクを管理している者だ
それをこのような
Yet, you would treat me this way!
Sorry about that.
すまないね　あんたの声が癇にさわるんだよ
Your voice just gets on my nerves, is all.
それと　禁煙中の男と話す時は気をつけたほうがいい
Also...
You should watch what you say when you talk to a man who's quit smoking.
見た目からは想像もつかないほどイラついてるからな
Despite his looks, he's always near his boiling point.
あんな応急処置で動くようになるのか
Will these makeshift repairs get it moving again?
しばらくはね
For a while, at least.
たまげたな　タフな機種とは聞いていたが
I'm amazed.
I'd always heard how tough a model this is.
できたぞ
I'm done.
ああ
Okay.
行くんだな
You're going, then?
ああ
Yeah.
そうか
All right.
じゃ勝手に死にに行け
Go get yourself killed, then!
こっちもできた
I'm done, too.
すまない
Thanks, and sorry.
謝るならナミに謝れよ
Tell that to Nami, not me.
宗介
Sousuke.
僕の正体は聞かないのかい
You're not going to ask about my identity?
察しはついてる
I've already guessed.
大方DGSEのエージェントだろ　フランスの
You're most likely a DGSE agent, from France.
当たりのようだな
Looks like I'm right.
お仲間は第29行動局の特殊部隊か
Your comrades must be part of the Action Division 29 special forces.
アマルガムの情報を探っていたんだろ
You were trying to gather intelligence on Amalgam, weren't you?
ああ
Yeah.
相良宗介　君はミスリルの兵士だろ
Sagara Sousuke.
You're a Mithril soldier?
元ミスリルだ
Former Mithril soldier.
今は違う
That's in the past.
どうだろう　ここは共闘してあのアマルガムの男を生捕りにしないか
What do you say about joining forces and capturing that Amalgam agent alive?
生捕りだと
Alive, you say?
奴が何をしたか知ってて言ってるのか
Are you aware of what he's done!?
だが貴重な情報源だ
Nevertheless, he's a valuable source of information.
クラマは俺の獲物だ　お前らの指図は受けない
Kurama is my prey.
I will not cooperate with you.
君の気持はわかる
I understand how you feel.
でも君だけで奴らを追い詰めるのはさすがに無理だよ
But going against those guys on your own?
That's impossible.
それでもやるしかない
Even so, I have to try.
しかし…
But...
ほかにどうしたらいいのかわからない
I don't know what else to do.
宗介　こちらも独自に作戦を進めるからな
Sousuke!
We're proceeding on with our operation.
勝手にしろ
Just stay out of my way.
行くぞ
Here goes.
こんな夜中に呼び出しやがって　あのくそ署長
Callin' us out here in the middle of the night.
That damn police chief.
Don't make a fuss. I hear we're gonna make bank.
そうくさるなよ　儲け話らしいぜ
Your attention!
傾注しろ
諸君への依頼は戦闘だ
Gentlemen, the reason I called you here is for combat.
Combat?
戦闘だ？
もうじき1機のASがこのナムサクへとやってくるだろう
We have word of an AS that is going to show up in Namsac shortly.
操縦者は危険なテロリストであり
The operator is a dangerous terrorist,
また薬物濫用で被害妄想にとりつかれておる
and is also in the grip of a drug-fueled paranoia.
そいつを殺せばいいんですかい
So we just need to kill the guy?
さよう
Correct.
この街に住む善良な市民に被害が及ぶ前に
Before any harm comes to the good people of this city,
そのテロリストを仕留めてもらいたい
I want you to bring down this terrorist.
奴を確実に殺すのだ
Just be sure to kill him.
Just one guy?
一人だけ？
そうだ
That's right.
Who the hell is he?
どこのどいつだ
相良宗介だ
He's Sagara Sousuke.
なに　相良だと
What?
Sagara, you say!?
そして　奴を葬った者には3万ドルを出す
Last but not least, I'll pay $30,000 to whoever gets the finishing blow!
マジか
そいつはえらく魅力的だが　ちょいと気前がよすぎねえかい
What a tempting offer...
but ain't it a little too generous?
I bet there's more to this.
裏がありそうだ
There's nothing you need to be concerned for, gentlemen.
諸君が気にする必要はない
I'll give you all the support you need.
必要な支援は全て与えてやる
すげえ　エリコンの最新型だぜ
Wow, that's the latest model Oerlikon.
OTO Melara, Mauser, Bofors... Talk about the works.
オットー・メララにマウザー　ボフォース　なんでもありだな
き…北に15キロの農村近くを白いサベージが通過したそうです
R-Reports say a white Savage
passed near a farming village 15 kilometers to the north.
Looks like he wants to fight after all.
やはり奴はやる気ですな
It's just as I told you.
言っただろう
だがまあ　あのチンピラどもが役に立つかどうかは怪しいところだがな
That being said, I have my doubts about these punks being of any use.
まさか　完全装備のASが10機ですぞ
Surely, you jest.
Those are ten fully-armed ASes.
Definitely, this time...
今度ばかりは…
I hope that's the case.
そう願ってるよ　こちらも準備はしておこうか
I might as well prepare, myself.
Prepare?
準備？
ゴール地点の準備だ　ここのことだよ
Prepare the finish line.
This place right here.
Kurama...
クラマ
A welcoming committee, huh?
歓迎委員会か
You're still here in this city, then.
奴はまだこの街にいる
止まれ
Halt!
来た
Here they come.
相良の野郎はこの先だ
Sagara's just up ahead.
ほとんど丸腰らしい
From what I heard, he's practically unarmed.
ついてるぜ　3万ドルはいただきだ
What luck!
That $30,000 is mine for the taking!
Hey, we agreed on 50-50!
おい　山分けだぞ　わかってんだろうな
You know that, right?
後ろ
Behind us!
You son of a bitch!
くそったれが
言え　あと何機いる
Talk. How many more mechs are there?
You—
さあ
やめろ　やめっ　8機だ　8機
Stop! Stop!
There are eight! Eight!
黒いコート姿の男を見たか　大柄の東洋人だ
Did you see a man wearing a black coat?
He's Asian, with a large build.
I saw him! At the arena with the police chief!
見た　闘技場で署長と
There he is!
いた
撃て　撃て
Open fire!
待て
Wait!
闘技場か
The arena...
相良の仕業か　大暴れだな
Is this Sagara's handiwork?
What a rampage.
今も戦っている　向こうだ
He's still fighting even now, over there.
邪魔をするな
Get out of my way!
Fire! Fire!
撃て　撃てー
What are you doing!?
何をしておる
相良
Sagara!
Dao!
ダオか
死ねー
時間は戻せないと知ってるよ
jikan wa modosenai to
I realize you can't
Die, Sagara!
死ね　相良
死にやがれ
Die, you bastard!
shitteru yo
turn back time.
信じたい気持ちを裏切られ
shinjitai kimochi wo uragerare
Even if the feelings I want to believe in are betrayed
mune no hane ga yaburetemo
and the wings in my heart are torn.
胸の羽が破れても
Ah! mukashi tonda ano aoi sora
Ah! That blue sky I once flew in
Ah!　昔　飛んだあの青い空
kawaranai kagayaki ni michite
is filled with an unchanging radiance.
変わらない輝きに満ちて
The mech's systems!
機体システムが…
"ubaitai nara ubaeba ii, sore ga"
"If you want to take it, just take it."
奪いたいなら　奪えばいい
くたばりやがれ
Go to hell!
それが愚かさだと　笑い飛ばしてやるさ
orokasa da to waraitobashite yaru sa
I'll laugh off the foolishness of those thoughts.
もう少しだけ動いてくれ
Just move... a little more!
何度倒れても　夢は消えないんだと
nando taoretemo yume wa kienain da to
For now, I bite my lip hard as I take the oath
Die!
死ねや
ima wa tsuyoku kuchibiru kande
that no matter how many times I fall, I'll never let my dream die.
いまは強く唇噛んで
dare ni mo tayorenai areta sekai no naka de
Even in this barren world devoid of allies,
誰にも頼れない　荒れた世界のなかで
moyasu no wa atsui kibou no SOUL
I set my fervently hopeful soul ablaze.
燃やすのは熱い希望の"SOUL"
時間は過ぎるだけで　戻らない
jikan wa sugiru dake de
Time merely passes.
modoranai
It never returns.
ナミ　最高の機体だった
Nami...
This mech really was the best.
Where are you?
どこだ
あの階段か
Up those stairs!?
更に上か
Still higher up!
He keeps retreating.
来ない　誘い込む気か
Is this a trap?
In that case!
なら
動く…
Don't mo—
下がれ　下がれ
Fall back! Fall back!
千鳥かなめはどこだ
Where's Kaname Chidori!?
聞いてどうする気だ
What are you gonna do if I tell you?
Rescue her!
助け出す
バカか　お前は
Are you stupid?
Say it!
言ってくれ
ごめんだね　歯ぎしりして死ぬがいい
No, thanks.
You can die in frustration.
教えてくれ
Tell me!
わからん　俺が貴様と相討ちだと　なぜだ
I don't get it.
You and I... gunning each other down?
Why is that?
彼女だ
Because of her!
愛の力ってやつか
Is that supposed to be the "power of love"?
笑わせるな
Don't make me laugh.
What the hell's wrong with that!?
何がいけない
サン・カルロス　じゃなきゃニケーロか　グラナダか
San Carlos.
If not that, Niquero, or Granada...
ほかには
Any others!?
知るか
How should I know?
禁煙なんてするんじゃなかっ…た
I knew I never should've quit smo...
...king...
サン・カルロス　ニケーロ　グラナ…
San Carlos...
Niquero...
Grana—
宗介
Sousuke!
挿管セット
Bring an intubation set!
エピネフリンとアトロピンもだ
And some epinephrine and atropine!
ナミ
Nami...
いや　千鳥
No...
Chidori...
会いたい…
I miss you...
寒い
I feel cold...
kimi ga yumemita sono ashita wa
That tomorrow you dreamed of
君が夢見た　その明日は
もう闇の中へ消えかけてる
mou yami no naka e kiekaketeru
is already starting to fade into the darkness.
淡い光に手を伸ばして
awai hikari ni te wo nobashite
I reach out toward the faint light
demo tsukamu mae ni hane wo mogare
but before I grasp it, my wings are plucked away.
でもつかむ前に　羽をもがれ
胸を駆け抜ける　僅かな幸せの日々
mune wo kakenukeru wazuka na shiawase no hibi
The days of fleeting happiness run through my mind.
失うと囁く予感は
ushinau to sasayaku yokan wa
I don't want to believe the foreboding whisper that I'll lose them.
shinjitakunai shinjitakunai
No, I don't want to believe.
信じたくない　信じたくない
aware na teikou da to shitemo
Even if it's pitiful resistance
哀れな抵抗だとしても
kiseki nozonde Remained
my wish for a miracle remained.
奇跡　望んで　Remained
きっかり時間通り　律儀ですな
Right on time.
Now that's integrity.
尾行は
Were you followed?
あったらここには来ていない
If I had, I wouldn't have come here.
But of course.
そりゃそうだ
Well then, the cargo.
では積み荷を
これが？
This is it?
Yes.
そうだ
よく回収できましたな
I'm impressed you managed to recover it.
警察も混乱していたからな
The police were distracted by all the chaos.
日本から運び出す時のほうが苦労した
It was much harder getting it out of Japan.
どうせです　こちらの積み荷もついでに見ていきますか
Since you're here, would you care to see the cargo before you go?
もちろん未完成ですが
Though, of course, it's still a work in progress.
こいつの名は
Does it have a name?
ないそうです
Officially, it does not.
もともと存在しない計画だったそうですからな
On paper, this project never existed in the first place.
ただ　まあ強いて番号を付けるなら
However, if I were to give it a code name,
ARX-8です
it would be the ARX-8.
Episode 9
The Fallen Witch
次回　堕ちた魔女
Next time: "The Fallen Witch."